What I want to do in this video is just give you
在本视频中 我将完整地展示
a complete overview of the app that we will be building.
我们即将构建的应用
So as you're building it with me,
因此当你与我一起构建时
you know exactly what we're doing.
将完全知道我们正在执行什么操作
So it's going to be a triathlon tracking app.
这将是一个铁人三项跟踪应用
So if you're not familiar with what a triathlon,
如果你不知道铁人三项是什么的话
is it's basically an event where you run, swim, and bike.
其实就是一项包含跑步 游泳和骑行的运动
On top of that, we're also going to track
此外 我们还将跟踪
our current meals or how we're eating for the specific day,
当前的三餐饮食或某一天的饮食情况
as well as how many hours of sleep we get.
以及睡眠时长
So you'll notice here that we have this history view.
这是一个历史记录视图
And for the day,
对于当天来说
if you don't log your information or if you haven't logged your information for this day,
如果你没有记录任何当天的信息
you're going to get a little reminder saying: hey,
系统将发出一条消息提醒
don't forget to log your information.
提示你别忘了记录信息
We can open up the calendar here and then we can
我们可以打开这里的日历
go ahead and scroll through this, if we wanted to.
并上下滚动
Let's select August 8th.
选择 8 月 8 日
When we select that, what we're going to get is every day from August 8th
当我们选择日期后 将显示 8 月 8 日
on as well as our specific data for that day.
及之后的每一天 并显示特定一天的数据
You'll notice here on August 12th,
你将注意到 在 8 月 12 日
we didn't log any data.
我们没有记录任何数据
So instead of getting a little card like this,
因此只出现一条消息：You didn't log any data on this day.
we just get: hey, you didn't log any data for this day.
而不是像这样的卡片
And let's go ahead and not leave Android out.
我们看看 Android 上的情况
It's going to be the exact same thing on Android.
在 Android 上是完全一样的
So now what we can do is we can click on one of these days and we get taken to this view.
点击某个日期并转到此视图
It has the date right here as the header, all of our information.
标题上是日期 这些是所有的信息
And allows us to also reset and clear the information for that specific day.
还可以重置并清空当天的信息
So now, on August 11th this will say: hey,
现在 8 月 11 日将提示
you didn't log any information because we cleared that.
你没有记录任何信息 因为我们清空了信息
So now, we can come on here and we can add a new entry.
我们可以转到这里并添加新的条目
This is how you add or log the specific information for the day.
这样就可以为当天添加或记录具体信息
You'll notice here that a few things are different.
你将注意到一些不同之处
The styles on iOS look a little bit different than on
iOS 上的样式与 Android 上的有所不同
Android just because they are two unique, distinct platforms.
因为它们是两个不一样的独特平台
So here, what we can do is we can come in here and we can
这里我们可以为当天记录一些信息
log some information for the current day. Submit that.
然后提交
And now, if we scroll up,
现在如果向上滚动
scrolling on the simulator is always a problem. So we go to the current day.
在模拟器上滚动总是不太理想 转到当前日期
And now we have the information that we just barely logged.
这里显示了刚刚记录的信息
And the last thing that we can do, and again,
最后一项操作是
if you come to the add entry screen after you logged your information,
如果你在记录信息后转到添加条目屏幕
you're going to get this view and this will say,
将转到此视图 它会提示
hey you're already logged your information.
嘿 你已经记录了信息
And the last screen, the screen is kind of fun,
最后一个屏幕比较有趣
what it's going to do is it's kind of like a real time tracker.
它就像一个实时跟踪器
So, it's going to tell you which way you're currently
它会告诉你当前正在朝着哪个方向前进
heading as well as your altitude and the current speed you're going.
以及海拔和行进速度
I have the simulator set to simulating a drive on the freeway, right now.
我现在将模拟器设置成了模拟高速驾驶状态
So you'll notice we are going 70 to 71 miles per hour.
你会看到现在是 70-71 英里/小时
We are currently heading West.
当前朝西前进
So that's basically the whole app that we're going to be building.
这就是我们即将构建的应用
There's a lot to it. It's a pretty big app.
有很多功能 是一个很庞大的应用
So there are a lot of videos of us building it.
因此会有很多讲解视频
But if you stick with it,
但是如果你能一直跟进学习进度
you will not be disappointed.
你不会失望的